export const quizQuestion = [
  {
    question: "What is the capital of France?",
    options: ["Berlin", "Madrid", "Paris", "Rome"],
    answer: "Paris",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country won the first FIFA World Cup in 1930?",
    options: ["Brazil", "Argentina", "Uruguay", "Germany"],
    answer: "Uruguay",
  },
  {
    question: "Who has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
    options: ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Pele", "Diego Maradona"],
    answer: "Lionel Messi",
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has won the most FIFA World Cups?",
    options: ["Germany", "Italy", "Brazil", "Argentina"],
    answer: "Brazil",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the all-time top scorer in the FIFA World Cup?",
    options: ["Miroslav Klose", "Ronaldo Nazário", "Pelé", "Cristiano Ronaldo"],
    answer: "Miroslav Klose",
  },
  // {
  //   question: "Which club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
  //   options: ["Manchester United", "FC Barcelona", "AC Milan", "Real Madrid"],
  //   answer: "Real Madrid",
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "Which player scored the 'Hand of God' goal in the 1986 FIFA World Cup?",
  //   options: ["Zinedine Zidane", "Diego Maradona", "Pele", "Johan Cruyff"],
  //   answer: "Diego Maradona",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is known as 'The Special One' in football management?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Pep Guardiola",
  //     "Jurgen Klopp",
  //     "Jose Mourinho",
  //     "Carlo Ancelotti",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Jose Mourinho",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which country won the ICC Cricket World Cup in 2019?",
  //   options: ["Australia", "India", "New Zealand", "England"],
  //   answer: "England",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who has scored the most centuries in international cricket?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Sachin Tendulkar",
  //     "Virat Kohli",
  //     "Ricky Ponting",
  //     "Jacques Kallis",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Sachin Tendulkar",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which player has taken the most wickets in Test cricket?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Muttiah Muralitharan",
  //     "Shane Warne",
  //     "James Anderson",
  //     "Anil Kumble",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Muttiah Muralitharan",
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "Who is the only cricketer to have scored 100 international centuries?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Ricky Ponting",
  //     "Virat Kohli",
  //     "Sachin Tendulkar",
  //     "Kumar Sangakkara",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Sachin Tendulkar",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which team won the first-ever T20 World Cup in 2007?",
  //   options: ["India", "Pakistan", "Australia", "West Indies"],
  //   answer: "India",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who has won the most IPL titles as a captain?",
  //   options: ["Rohit Sharma", "MS Dhoni", "Virat Kohli", "Gautam Gambhir"],
  //   answer: "Rohit Sharma",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which cricketer is known as 'The Wall'?",
  //   options: ["Virat Kohli", "Rahul Dravid", "Sunil Gavaskar", "Steve Waugh"],
  //   answer: "Rahul Dravid",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which football club is known as 'The Red Devils'?",
  //   options: ["Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Arsenal", "Bayern Munich"],
  //   answer: "Manchester United",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who won the Golden Boot in the 2022 FIFA World Cup?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Lionel Messi",
  //     "Kylian Mbappe",
  //     "Harry Kane",
  //     "Cristiano Ronaldo",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Kylian Mbappe",
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "Who was the first cricketer to hit six sixes in an over in international cricket?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Yuvraj Singh",
  //     "Herschelle Gibbs",
  //     "Chris Gayle",
  //     "Shahid Afridi",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Herschelle Gibbs",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Which footballer is known as 'El Pistolero'?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Luis Suárez",
  //     "Karim Benzema",
  //     "Sergio Aguero",
  //     "Edinson Cavani",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Luis Suárez",
  // },
  // {
  //   question:
  //     "Which cricketer has the highest individual score in One Day Internationals (ODIs)?",
  //   options: [
  //     "Virender Sehwag",
  //     "Martin Guptill",
  //     "Chris Gayle",
  //     "Rohit Sharma",
  //   ],
  //   answer: "Rohit Sharma",
  // },
  // {
  //   question: "Who is the only footballer to have won three FIFA World Cups?",
  //   options: ["Diego Maradona", "Pelé", "Zinedine Zidane", "Ronaldo Nazário"],
  //   answer: "Pelé",
  // },
];
